livemixtapes.com 2019-02-18

# Privacy Policy - LiveMixtapes.com

**Privacy Policy**  
At Livemixtapes.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. The information we collect about you is used to provide you with a more personalized and richer experience while visiting our site. Please read further for details. 

**How Does Livemixtapes.com Collect Information?**  
Your IP Address   
Your IP address is a unique identifier we use to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website tracking. We also use your IP address to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad, demographic information. 

**Cookies**  
Livemixtapes.com uses a feature on your Internet Web browser called a "cookie." A cookie is a small piece of information stored on your hard drive. It assigns a unique identification number to your computer and helps us maintain your preferences between visits to provide a personalized experience for you. Livemixtapes.com uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to tell us whether or not you have visited our Website before. We also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous session numbers, with them. 

**What About Personal Information? Do You Collect That?**  
Livemixtapes.com does not house or collect any personal information about you unless you knowingly and willingly provide it. 

**Membership Registration**  
Livemixtapes.com has a registration process through which you voluntarily sign up to access the members-only features of our Website. During the registration process, we ask for your name, email address, and other personal information. To make sure that nobody else can access our members-only features using your name or identity, we ask that you create a unique username with a password. 

**Newsletter Subscription***  
Livemixtapes.com sends one email newsletter a week which will include a list of our newest or top videos and a few featured news articles or contest updates. From time to time, we may also send an email notifying you of an upcoming contest or special features. We give you the choice whether to receive email or other contact from us and we give you the opportunity to unsubscribe from receiving unwanted communications.

*We do not currently run any type of newsletters. **Contests and Promotions**  
When you enter a contest or take part in a promotion, we may ask for your name, mailing address and email address. Should a third party sponsor the contest or promotion, that party will have access to this information. We need this information in order to notify our winners and, when applicable, ship the winners' prizes. **Does Livemixtapes.com Ever Share Information with Other Parties?**  
Disclosure of Information to Outside Parties   
Livemixtapes.com may provide your email information to select partners, reputable companies or organizations whose products and services may interest you. If you prefer not to receive online marketing from Livemixtapes.com, please contact us at [contact@Livemixtapes.com](mailto:contact@livemixtapes.com). We do collect demographic and profile data, which is aggregated and shared with advertisers. 

**Personal Information We Collect From You**

By registering with, or providing personal information, to a Site, as well as providing permission to receive marketing offers, users allow us and our affiliates to make their personally identifiable information available to third parties in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. While you are visiting a Site, we may collect “Personal Information” from you. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, Personal Information shall mean individually identifiable information from or about an individual including, but not limited to: (a) a first and last name; (b) a home or other physical address, including street name and name of city or town; (c) an e-mail address or other online contact information, such as an instant messaging user identifier or a screen name that reveals an individual’s e-mail address; (d) a telephone number; (e) a persistent identifier, such as a customer number held in a cookie or processor serial number, that is combined with other available data that identifies an individual; (f) age; (h) income level; (g) hobbies, buying patterns or preferences; or (h) any other information from or about an individual that is combined with any of (a) through (i) above.

To the extent that user credit card-specific information is collected by us, any of our affiliates and/or subsidiaries, said information will be kept in confidence and will not be shared with any third parties (other than consumer credit agencies or third parties in order to process a purchase of goods and/or services) without the user's prior informed consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we, our affiliates and/or subsidiaries reserve the right to share with third parties the fact that they have credit card information on file for specific users but they will not share the specific credit card information with third parties without the user's prior informed consent.

**How We Use Personal Information**

This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from us, or any of our partner Sites, via e-mail, via third party partner Sites or otherwise. We may sell the Personal Information that you supply to us to any third party and we may work with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our users. These businesses and third parties may include, but are not limited to: (a) providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation; (b) e-mail marketers; and (c) telemarketers. 

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from user lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our users’ Personal Information as needed to perform their functions for us but we do not permit them to use your Personal Information for other purposes.

Additionally, we purchase and manage e-mail lists generated by affiliate Sites and organizations. Users may remove themselves from a specific mailing list by utilizing the unsubscribe options that are present and available at the end of each piece of e-mail that we send.

We will also use your Personal Information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience on a Site and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you on a Site. We may also use your Personal Information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources. We may use third parties to help us operate our business and the Sites or administer activities on our behalf. We also reserve the right to release current or past user information in the event that we believe that the user is using, or has used, our products, services and/or Site(s): (i) in violation of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy or any other of our operating rules, policies, price schedules and other supplemental terms and conditions or documents that may be published by us from time to time; (ii) to commit unlawful acts; (iii) if such information is subpoenaed; (iv) if we are sold or acquired; (v) or when we deem it necessary or appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission implementing regulations. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we reserve the right to share, sell, rent, lease and/or otherwise distribute any and all personal information with/to any third party for any and all uses permitted by this Privacy Policy and applicable law. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we agree not to share the Social Security Number of California State residents with third-parties without first obtaining the consent of such California residents pursuant to the terms and conditions set forth in the California Financial Privacy Act (“CFPA”). 

In addition, by registering at any of the Sites, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the (“Rule”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations .  Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed at the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telephone in accordance with the Rule and the applicable state do-not-call regulations. You may unsubscribe from any of our e-mail marketing programs at any time. In every e-mail communication we send, there is an unsubscribe hyperlink that allows the recipient to unsubscribe from the specific marketing program by simply clicking the hyperlink provided and following the instructions that follow. We attempt to process all unsubscribe requests in a prompt fashion. However, after unsubscribing, we cannot guarantee that you will never receive another mailing from us, because we may obtain your e-mail address in the future through a different e-mail marketing program that you have opted into. We can guarantee, however, that if you should ever receive another e-mail communication from us, you will be able to remove your e-mail address via the unsubscribe hyperlink. We are able to offer our free services, in part, based upon the willingness of our users to be contacted by our marketing partners, including affiliated third party advertisers. By allowing us to make the information you supply available to our marketing partners, you will receive free product and service information that may be of interest to you.?You may, at any time, notify us that you do not wish to have your Personal Information disclosed to third parties for offers and promotions by sending an e-mail to [contact@livemixtapes.com](mailto:contact@livemixtapes.com)

**Marketing Partners**

We may share, license or sell your information to third parties for various marketing purposes, including their online (e.g., e-mail marketing) and offline (e.g., telemarketing, cell phone text messaging, skip tracing, and direct mail) marketing programs. If you would like to be removed from these programs, click here and follow the opt-out instructions. By filling out or submitting a registration form or partial registration form you are consenting to receive offers from us and third marketers via email, telemarketing postal mail and or SMS text message wireless or other mobile offering to your cell phone. You understand that your wireless carrier's standard charges and rates apply to these messages. For SMS text messages, you may remove our information by replying "STOP", "END", OR "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request.

**Links to Outside Third Parties**  
Livemixtapes.com may establish relationships with reputable business partners by creating a link between our sites. Livemixtapes.com chooses its business partners carefully. We are not, however, responsible for the content, maintenance or privacy policies of those sites. Once you click over to a third-party site, we encourage you to check their privacy policy. Users who click over to a third-party site from a link on Livemixtapes.com must be aware that Livemixtapes.com makes no warranties with regard to that site's policies or business practices. Livemixtapes.com is not responsible for any transactions that occur between the user and the third-party site. Should a user purchase any products or services from that third-party site, the user must contact the third-party site directly regarding any disputes that might occur, including, but not limited to: delayed shipping, missing products, damaged goods, or pricing or billing discrepancies. Livemixtapes.com is not responsible for the actions of any third-party site. **Children's Guidelines**  
Livemixtapes.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet use. Also, we strongly encourage parents to help us enforce our privacy policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information on this site without permission. **Public Forums**  
Livemixtapes.com has real-time comments available to its users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. As these forums are public and open for users to interact with each other, Livemixtapes.com expects all its users to respect the rights of others. **Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, email us contact@livemixtapes.com. **LiveMixtapes Mobile App**  
In addition to other information described in this policy, we may collect and share precise location information, through methods such as mobile “SDKs”. This location information may be used by itself, aggregated, or combined with mobile identifiers (such as IDFAs and Android IDs), and shared with third parties, for purposes related to advertising, attribution (e.g., measuring ad performance) analytics and research. You can remove your consent to having your location data collected by changing the settings on your device.(Certain services may lose functionality as a result.) You can opt-out from any interest-based advertising through your device settings. When you have opted out using this setting on a device, advertisers will not use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests or serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.  **Subscribe/unsubscribe**  
Should you choose to in the future, Livemixtapes.com provides its users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners. 

If you would like to cancel your registered membership, remove your information from our database and not receive future communications from us, please utilize one of the following options: Email your request to [contact@livemixtapes.com](mailto:contact@livemixtapes.com)

Send your request via post to: 

Correct/Update   
If you would like to change or modify information you previously provided to us, please utilize one of the following options: Email your request to 

Send your request via post to: 

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Website, you may contact: [contact@livemixtapes.com](mailto:contact@livemixtapes.com)
